Guide to the Gordon Moore Papers M1965
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 2: Chronological Files, 1958-2003
  - Sub-Series I: Correspondence, Minutes and Other Material affiliated with Gordon Moore, 1958-2003
    - Association for Corporate Growth Meeting - Correspondence, Pamphlet, Notes re: Holding a Tiger by the Tail (also used for Stanford Business Alumni) [Originally in Box 12, Folder 14], 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - National Computer Conference (NCC) - re: “Toward the Computer of Tomorrow,” Correspondence, Notes, Forms [Originally in Box 12, Folder 15], 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - European Solid State Device Research Conference (ESSDERC)- Overhead Transparencies, Diagrams, Presentation Slides, Notes, Correspondence, Research Papers re: Future Directions of Silicon Device Technology (1 of 2) [Originally in Box 13, Folder 1], 1977 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - European Solid State Device Research Conference (ESSDERC) Notebook - Agenda, Program, Correspondence, Presentation Slides, Notes (2 of 2) [Originally in Box 13, Folder 2], 1977 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Intel Corp. Correspondence, Presentation Slides, Programs, Research Paper, Graphs, Notes re: “Who’s Going to Use All Those Functions?” for Dataquest Semiconductor Industry Service Conference [Originally in Box 13, Folder 4], October 1977 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - General Electric Microprocessor Symposium Presentation - Correspondence, Notes [Originally in Box 13, Folder 5], October 1977 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - IEEE Correspondence, Brochure, Articles re: Robert Noyce receiving Cledo Brunetti Award at International Solid State Circuits Conference [Originally in Box 13, Folder 6], 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Intel Corp. Long Range Planning Sessions - Correspondence, Schedules [Originally in Box 13, Folder 7], 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Intel Corp. Presentation Slides, Overhead Transparencies, Graphs, Notes for Insurance Group Meeting at Marriott re: A New Basic Industry Semiconductor Device Manufacture [Originally in Box 13, Folder 8], March 1978 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Financial Analysts Federation Conference on High Technology - Brochures, Overhead Transparencies, Graphs, Notes, Correspondence [Originally in Box 13, Folder 9], March 1978 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Caltech Management Seminar - Pamphlets, Notes, Presentation Slides [Originally in Box 13, Folder 10], March 1978 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Electronics Components Conference - Correspondence, Brochures, Notes, Program [Originally in Box 13, Folder 11], April 1978 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Intel Corp. Shareholders Meeting - Presentation Notes [Originally in Box 13, Folder 12], April 1978 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Litton Industries Advanced Electronics Conference - Correspondence, Notes re: Microcomputer Technology [Originally in Box 13, Folder 13], May 1978 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Intel Corp. National Computer Conference Panel and Harry Goode Award for Robert Noyce and Gordon Moore - Correspondence, Pamphlet, Presentation Notes, Graphs re: Impact on Semiconductor Technology on Computer Architecture; News release on MCS 86 microprocessor [Originally in Box 14, Folder 1], June 1978 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Intel Corp. Quarterly Dinner Meeting - Correspondence, Chart [Originally in Box 14, Folder 2], June 1978 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Intel Corp. Hillsboro, Oregon Groundbreaking Site - Pamphlets, Articles, Map re: Oregon, Presentation Notes [Originally in Box 14, Folder 3], July 1978 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Intel Corp. Manila/Penang Presentation - Overhead Transparencies, Graphs, Presentation Slides, Newsletters re: 10 Year Anniversary of Intel Corp. [Originally in Box 14, Folder 4], August 1978 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Intel Corp. Research Paper re: Microcomputer Comes Out of the Closet [Originally in Box 14, Folder 5], September 1978 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - National Academy of Science Computers and Communication Panel for Five Year Outlook - Correspondence, Research Paper re: Microcomputers [Originally in Box 14, Folder 6], September 1978 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Intel Corp. Compensation and Benefits M3D Seminars - Correspondence, Notes, Overhead Transparencies, Diagrams, Graphs [Originally in Box 14, Folder 7], 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Portland State University Masters of Business Administration Update - Correspondence, Notes, Brochure [Originally in Box 14, Folder 10], 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - San Jose State University Management of High Technology Seminar - Correspondence [Originally in Box 14, Folder 11], 1979 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Caltech (VLSI) Very Large Scale Integration Symposium, International Solid State Circuits Conference (ISSCC) - Research Papers, Correspondence, Articles, Graphs, Notes re: Are We Really Ready for VLSI2 (1 of 2) [Originally in Box 15, Folder 1], February 1979 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - International Solid State Circuits Conference - Research Papers, Notes, Program, Correspondence re: Frederik Philips Award (2 of 2) [Originally in Box 15, Folder 2], 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Bank of America Achievement Award Panel - Programs, Correspondence [Originally in Box 15, Folder 3], March 1979 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Dean Witter Reynolds Inc. European Investment Managers Meeting - Correspondence, Presentation Slides [Originally in Box 15, Folder 5], March 1979 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - MRI Systems Corporation ASTUTE Conference (Association of SYSTEM 2000 Users for Technical Exchange) - Notes, Correspondence, Research Paper, Program, Agenda [Originally in Box 15, Folder 6], April 1979 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Intel Corp. Annual Shareholders Meeting - Notes, Overhead Transparencies [Originally in Box 15, Folder 7], April 1979 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Financial Analysts Federation (FAF) Conference - Correspondence (to Robert Noyce), Notes re: Microelectronics, Program [Originally in Box 15, Folder 8], May 1979 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Computer and Communications Industry Association Quarterly Membership and Board of Directors Meeting - Notes, Overhead Transparencies, Agenda, Presentation Slides re: Availability of Leading Edge Component Technology, Pamphlets, Executive Perspective Booklet [Originally in Box 15, Folder 10], June 1979 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Montgomery Securities Investment Conference - Overhead Transparencies, Presentation Slides, Correspondence, Notes, Program, Graphs [Originally in Box 16, Folder 2], September 1979 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Intel Corp. Board of Directors Meeting - Overhead Transparencies, Agenda, Minutes, Notes, Capital Projects Request for Authorization [Originally in Box 16, Folder 3], 1979 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Electronics Panel - Correspondence re: 50th Anniversary [Originally in Box 16, Folder 4], September 1979 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Semiconductor Equipment and Materials Institute (SEMI) Panel - Correspondence, Notes, Presentation Slides, Graphs re: Very Large Scale Integration [Originally in Box 16, Folder 5], October 1979 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Bell Telephone Laboratories Visit to Intel Corp - Overhead Transparencies, Notes, Correspondence, Booklet of Presentation Slides [Originally in Box 16, Folder 6], November 1979 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Intel Corp. College Recruiter Training Seminar re: Introductory Remarks - Overhead Transparencies, Notes, Correspondence, Presentation Slides, Graphs [Originally in Box 16, Folder 7], 1979 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - American Association for the Advancement of Science 1980 Annual Meeting, General Interest Lecture - Notes, Research Paper re: Technology: Past, Present, and Future, Correspondence, Program [Originally in Box 16, Folder 8], 1979-1980 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - University of California, Berkeley Meeting - Correspondence, Research Papers re: Microelectronics, Campus Map, Program re: Second Industrial Liaison Meeting [Originally in Box 17, Folder 1], January 1980 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Houston Society of Financial Analysts - Correspondence, Notes, Presentation Slides [Originally in Box 17, Folder 2], 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Intel Corp. Correspondence, Agenda, Presentation Slides re: Xerox Corporation/El Segundo Crush Briefing [Originally in Box 17, Folder 3], February 1980 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Intel Corp. Correspondence re: G.S. Grumman and Cowen & Company Meeting [Originally in Box 17, Folder 4], March 1980 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Intel Corp. Notes, Correspondence re: ASQC talk - Future Trends in Large Scale Integration Technology and Reliability Issues [Originally in Box 17, Folder 6], March 1980 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Intel Corp. Opening of Albuquerque, New Mexico Plant - Correspondence, Agenda, Briefing Paper [Originally in Box 17, Folder 7], April 1980 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Rosen Research Inc. and Morgan Stanley Tenth Annual Semiconductor Forum - Correspondence, Agendas, Program, Newsletters, Corporate Net Bookings, Research Papers re: Semiconductor Industry and Market, Overhead Transparencies (1 of 2) [Originally in Box 17, Folder 10], May 1980 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Rosen Research Inc. and Morgan Stanley Tenth Annual Semiconductor Forum - Correspondence, Agendas, Program, Notes, Overhead Transparencies, Research Papers re: Intel Corp. and Wells Fargo Bank Indenture, Intel Corp. Resolutions Adopted by Board of Directors, Intel Corp. Underwriting Agreements (2 of 2) [Originally in Box 17, Folder 11], May 1980 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - National Science Foundation Working Group on Information Technology of the Advisory Committee for Information Science and Technology - Correspondence, Program Reports, Programs [Originally in Box 18, Folder 1], 1980-1982 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Santa Clara County Manufacturing Group Energy Conference re: Electricity in Silicon Valley: Summer 1980 and Beyond - Correspondence, Program, Intel Corp. Energy Management Progress Report, Dun’s Review: American Beauties for the ‘80s [Originally in Box 18, Folder 2], July 1980 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Intel Corp. Underwriting Group and Rating Agencies (Financial Communities) - Overhead Transparencies, Presentation Slides, Agendas, Correspondence [Originally in Box 18, Folder 4], 1980 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - College Relations Kickoff - Notes [Originally in Box 18, Folder 5], September 1980 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Dataquest Semiconductor Industry Conference re: Software Challenge of the 80s - Presentation, Notes, Presentation Slides, Articles, Agendas, Correspondence, Program, Brochure [Originally in Box 18, Folder 6], October 1980 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Intel Corp. Bank Meeting - Overhead Transparencies, Notes, Correspondence, Presentation Slides, Graphs [Originally in Box 18, Folder 7], 1980 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Investment Analysts Society of Chicago Presentation - Overhead Transparencies, Notes, Correspondence [Originally in Box 18, Folder 8], 1980 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Government Microcircuit Applications Conference re: Very High Speed Integrated Circuits - Correspondence, Reports, Notes, Program [Originally in Box 18, Folder 9], 1980 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Anti-Defamation League Torch of Liberty Award-B’nai B’rith - Correspondence, Notes [Originally in Box 18, Folder 10], 1980-1981 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Brookings Institution Conference for Federal Executives on Business Policy and Operations - Presentation Slides, Notes, Program [Originally in Box 18, Folder 11], February 1981 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Intel Corp. Strategic Long Range Plan ’81 - Notes re: Overhead Transparencies [Originally in Box 19, Folder 1], 1981 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Semiconductor Industry Association Statistical Reviews Quarterly Analysis of Semiconductor Markets [Originally in Box 19, Folder 2], 1981-1988 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Electrochemical Society, Inc. - Program, Correspondence, Graphs, Notes re: A Perspective on Very Large Scale Integration [Originally in Box 19, Folder 3], May 1981 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Intel Corp. Analysts Meeting - Correspondence [Originally in Box 19, Folder 5], July 1981 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Intel Corp. Andre Giraud Visit - Correspondence, Resume, Presentation Slides [Originally in Box 19, Folder 8], September 1981 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Financial Analysts Federation Second Industrial Revolution: Innovation Through Technology Conference: Correspondence, Agenda, Program, Notes [Originally in Box 19, Folder 12], 1981-1982 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Intel Corp. Strategic Planning Training/SBS (Small Business Server?) re: Memory Components - Correspondence, Presentation Slides [Originally in Box 19, Folder 13], 1981-1982 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Intel Corp. Institutional Dinner, New York Society of Financial Analysts Meeting - Notes, Presentation Slides, Correspondence [Originally in Box 19, Folder 15], 1982 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Intel Corp. Board of Directors and Shareholders Meeting - Newsletters, Agendas, Correspondence, Management Letter, Presentation Slides, Minutes, Notes, Overhead Transparencies [Originally in Box 20, Folder 1], 1981-1982 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Intel Corp. Northern Europe Headquarters - Agendas, Correspondence, Graphs, Research Papers re: British Telecom, March (1 of 2) [Originally in Box 20, Folder 2], 1982 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Intel Corp. Northern Europe Headquarters Trip - Presentation Slides and Notes re: “Intel is Winning by Design,” Correspondence, Agendas, Minutes of Meetings with Rob Wilmott of ICL (International Computers Limited), John Whyte, British Telecom Enterprises, News clippings, Articles (2 of 2) [Originally in Box 20, Folder 3], 1982 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Financial Executives Institute (FEI) - Correspondence, Presentation Slides, Overhead Transparencies, Notes [Originally in Box 20, Folder 4], April 1982 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - University of Portland Commencement Address - Program, Notes, Correspondence, Catalog, Maps [Originally in Box 20, Folder 7], May 1982 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - IEEE Managing the Flow of Technical Information, An Industry/Government Dialogue, National Academy of Sciences Panel - Program, Correspondence, Agenda, Articles re: Soviet Union Technology, Notes [Originally in Box 20, Folder 9], June 1982 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Intel Corp. London Conferences - LFRUT (L.F. Rothschild, Unterberg, Towbin) European Investors Meeting re: Struggle for Technological Leadership; Financial Times Conference on World Electronics - Research Papers re: The US, Champion Under Pressure?, Presentation Slides, Agendas, Correspondence, Program, Pamphlet (1 of 2) [Originally in Box 21, Folder 1], June 1982 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Intel Corp. London Conferences - LFRUT European Investors Meeting re: Struggle for Technological Leadership; Financial Times Conference on World Electronics - Agenda, Notes, Programs, Correspondence (2 of 2) [Originally in Box 21, Folder 2], 1982 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Intel Corp. Board of Directors Meeting - Agenda, Correspondence, Minutes, Presentation Slides [Originally in Box 21, Folder 4], July 1982 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - International Solid State Circuits Conference Evening Panel on Joint Research and Development - Correspondence, Program, Research Papers for Panel, Notes [Originally in Box 21, Folder 7], 1982-1983 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Dataquest Semiconductor Industry Service Conference Binder - Agenda, Program, Presentation Summaries [Originally in Box 22, Folder 2], October 1982 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Computers in Science Conference - Notes, Correspondence, Program [Originally in Box 22, Folder 5], December 1982 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - International Solid State Circuits Conference Related Events re: McGraw-Hill Editors, Electronics Analyst Splinter group - Correspondence, Presentation Notes, Articles [Originally in Box 22, Folder 7], February 1983 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Caltech Venture Capital and Entrepreneurship Seminar - Correspondence, Map, Agenda [Originally in Box 22, Folder 9], February 1983 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - University of California, Berkeley Presentation on Crisis in Microelectronics/Japanese Capital Investments - Research Papers, Notes, Graphs, Overhead Transparencies, Correspondence [Originally in Box 22, Folder 11], February 1983 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - National Science Foundation Interagency Conference for Small Firms on Federal Research and Development (High Tech ‘83) - Notes, Correspondence, Program, Workbook [Originally in Box 23, Folder 1], March 1983 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - National Sales Conference, Hambrecht and Quist Technology Conference - Notes, Correspondence [Originally in Box 23, Folder 3], May 1983 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Intel Corp. European Trip re: Siemens IC Division, Plessey Telecomm, International Federation for Information Processing World Computer Congress - Correspondence, Agendas, Programs, Notes, Research Papers re: Future Trend of Microprocessor by Tomihiro Matsumura, Presentation Notes re: Evolution of Microprocessor [Originally in Box 23, Folder 7], 1981-1983 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Intel Corp. Distributor Presidents Conference - Agenda, Program, Brochure, Correspondence, Notes [Originally in Box 23, Folder 8], October 1983 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Intel Corp. United Way and Open Forum in Oregon - Correspondence, Overhead Transparencies, Presentation Slides [Originally in Box 23, Folder 9], October 1983 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Dataquest Semiconductor Industry Conference - Notes, Program, Correspondence, Brochure, Presentation Slides, Transcript re: Very Large Scale Integration Complexity Crisis: October 1983 Dataquest Semiconductor Industry Service Conference Binder - Agenda, Program, Presentation Summaries [Originally in Box 24, Folder 1] (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Dataquest Semiconductor Industry Service Conference Binder - Agenda, Program, Presentation Summaries: October 1983 Regis McKenna Inc. Semiconductor Memory Forum - Correspondence, Transcripts, Presentation Slides re: How the Memory Business is Changing [Originally in Box 24, Folder 2], February 1984 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Regis McKenna Inc. Semiconductor Memory Forum - Correspondence, Transcripts, Presentation Slides re: How the Memory Business is Changing [Originally in Box 25, Folder 2], February 1984 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - American Electronics Association Meeting - Correspondence, Notes, Graphs, Overhead Transparencies re: Economic View of Semiconductor Manufacturer [Originally in Box 25, Folder 5], February 1984 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - University of California, Davis Presentation re: Technological Leadership for California and the Nation - Presentation Slides, Notes, Correspondence, Overhead Transparencies, Program, Graphs (Regis McKenna Info was moved to 10/ 18) [Originally in Box 26, Folder 1], April 1984 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Multibus Manufacturers Group - Notes, Overhead Transparencies, Correspondence [Originally in Box 26, Folder 2], April 1984 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Intel Corp. Sales Training Meeting - Correspondence, Presentation Slides, Agenda [Originally in Box 26, Folder 5], May 1984 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Wyle Laboratories Presentation - Notes, Presentation Slides, Correspondence re: Olympic pins [Originally in Box 26, Folder 6], June 1984 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Intel Corp. Board of Directors Meeting - Minutes, Presentation Slides, Agenda, Capital Project Authorizations [Originally in Box 26, Folder 7], July 1984 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - American Electronics Association (AEA) Executive Institute - Correspondence, Program, Notes [Originally in Box 26, Folder 9], August 1984 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Intel Corp. Visit to Northern Telecom - Correspondence, Agenda [Originally in Box 26, Folder 11], August 1984 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - BACUS (Bay Area Chrome Users Society) Symposium - Notes, Correspondence, Presentation Slides re: Masks for Very Large Scale Integration, Program [Originally in Box 26, Folder 13], September 1984 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Intel Corp. M-4 Managing Our Cyclical Business - Presentation Slides, Correspondence, Memo Notepad, Overhead Transparencies [Originally in Box 27, Folder 2], October 1984 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Dataquest Semiconductor Industry Service Conference Binder - Agenda, Program, Presentation Summaries, Presentation Slides (1 of 2) [Originally in Box 27, Folder 3], October 1984 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Dataquest Semiconductor Industry Service Conference Binder - Agenda, Program, Presentation Summaries, Presentation Slides (2 of 2) [Originally in Box 27, Folder 4], October 1984 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Intel Corp. Presidents Conference - Correspondence [Originally in Box 27, Folder 6], November 1984 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - IEEE Centennial Events including Technology Policy Conference, Centennial Convocations, Keys to the Future Forum - Notes, Correspondence, Programs, Newsletter, News Supplement The Institute, Robert Noyce Presentation, David Packard Presentation [Originally in Box 28, Folder 1], 1984 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Intel Corp. Black and White Stats (Printed Cards) [Originally in Box 28, Folder 2], undated (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Intel Corp. Presentation Slides, Overhead Transparencies re: Proposal for Establishing Center for Robotic Systems in Microelectronics at University of California, Berkeley College of Engineering [Originally in Box 28, Folder 3], January 1985 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Intel Corp. Board of Directors Meeting - Correspondence, Presentation Slides, Capital Project Authorization, Overhead Transparencies (2 of 2) [Originally in Box 28, Folder 5], January 1985 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Bay Area Council Outlook Conference - Correspondence, Pamphlets, Brochures, Newspaper Clippings, Presentation Notes re: Electronics: Can Silicon Valley Maintain its Technological Edge? [Originally in Box 28, Folder 7], 1984-1985 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Stanford Research Institute International Annual Board and Council Meeting - Agenda, Program re: Metallic Glasses, Brochure, The SRI Journal Newspaper [Originally in Box 28, Folder 8], March 1985 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Symposium on Economics and Technology re: Entrepreneurship - Transcript of Gordon Moore Presentation, Vernon Ruttan Presentation, Robert Swanson Presentation, Notes, Correspondence, Brochure, Research Paper re: Impacts of Microelectronics Revolution on Japan’s Industrial Structure and Business Society by Chikashi Moriguchi, Research Paper re: Public Policies to Foster High Technology Growth by Alan Wolff, Articles [Originally in Box 29, Folder 1], March 1985 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Symposium on Economics and Technology re: Entrepreneurship - Photocopied Articles given by Ralph Landau for preparation of symposium [Originally in Box 29, Folder 2], 1984 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Intel Corp. Board of Directors and Annual Shareholders Meeting - Overhead Transparencies, Minutes, Notes, Andrew Grove Slide List (same list used for Israel trip), Transcript, Correspondence, Presentation Slides, Capital Project Authorizations, Agenda, Graphs (1 of 2) [Originally in Box 29, Folder 3], March 1985 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Intel Corp. Israel Fab - Correspondence, Overhead Transparencies, Agenda, Presentation Slides, Notes, Trip Report [Originally in Box 29, Folder 5], April 1985 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Intel Corp. Technical Strategy Seminar, Asilomar Conference Center - Correspondence, Overhead Transparencies, Maps [Originally in Box 30, Folder 2], April 1985 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Intel Corp. M-4 Managing Our Cyclical Business - Overhead Transparencies, Presentation Slides, Graphs [Originally in Box 30, Folder 3], April 1985 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - University of New Mexico Commencement Speech re: A Revolution in Progress - Notes, Correspondence [Originally in Box 30, Folder 4], May 1985 (Box 14, Folder 3)